paytoo.com 2010-12-01

# Paytoo - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website.  Please read this Privacy Notice and our Privacy Code of Conduct before using our website, submitting any personal data, or becoming a customer.  By using this website or our services you agree to these terms. Each Paymotech Group Company or DBA websites have their own separate Policies and Procedures. If Paymotech Group uses third parties to provide services on its behalf, we will request that such third parties protect your sensitive information in a manner consistent with our policies.  This policy and the code of conduct dated *** are subject to change without notice by posting a revision on this website. It is the responsibility of visitors to this website to refer to this page from time to time to review any subsequent amendments.

Our website may contain links to third party websites which are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Paymotech Groups not responsible for the actions of third party websites.  If you have any questions regarding these policies and practices please contact [privacy@paymotech.com](mailto:privacy@yackietelecom.com) .

### Your Privacy Is Our Concern

At Paymotech Group, your privacy is our concern. We understand your desire for privacy and secure communications and we have developed our Privacy Notice in order to help you understand the steps we take to protect your sensitive personal information. Our Privacy Policies and Procedures demonstrate our commitment to privacy and security. We want you to feel confident about the privacy and security of your personal information.

### Your Privacy

Paymotech Group collects information to comply with laws and regulations, to be able to offer you enhanced service options for your consideration, open accounts, provide services, provide you an accounting for those services, protect the systems used to provide services, and to fight fraud and abuse.

Paymotech Group’s policies, people, and technology protect your privacy and your sensitive personal data as carefully as we protect our company’s sensitive corporate data using our best efforts and by relying on you to protect your passwords and otherwise help us to protect your data.  Paymotech Group does not share, disclose, trade or sell any personally identifiable information collected online with other unrelated companies or organizations. If Paymotech Group should, at any time, desire to share its customers' sensitive personal or online transactional data with unrelated third parties, it will provide advance notification allowing its users an opportunity to opt out preventing the company from providing their information to third parties.  Customers may not opt out from receiving information which is critical for providing services, maintaining or updating customer’s accounts or where legally required or normally permitted.  Disclosure for Legal Purposes: While Paymotech Group will use its best efforts to protect your privacy and personal information, we may be required by law or we may believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary: a) to defend our rights or property or those of our users; b) to comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; c) or in connection with a corporate transaction such as a merger, consolidation or sale of substantial assets.

**Improper Conduct:** We may also use your personal information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activity that threatens our service.

**Personal Information:**

We do not collect any personal information from a visitor to our site unless that visitor explicitly and intentionally provides it. Under no circumstances do we collect any personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life. If you are simply browsing our site, we do not gather any personal information about you.

Paymotech Group may ask you for personally identifiable information such as your name, address, telephone number or email address. We use this information to help maintain accurate accounts and provide the services you have requested.  
Any details that you provide to us are stored for use on future visits, as we do not want you to give us any information more than once. Personally identifiable information that we collect may be stored and processed in any country where Paymotech Group or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. Personally identifiable information may be combined with other information about your use of our sites in order to improve our services and products. Some examples of how we might use your personal information include:  Our server will recognize your domain name and the pages that you visit. This data is gathered for quality control and improvement of our site. When an email is sent to us, we will use your email address in order to respond to your enquiry. We collect information that you volunteer to us on surveys, contests, and registration sites. We ask for your email address in order to communicate with you about your account and other Paymotech Group related services and products. We may also contact you to offer new products and services. However if you do not want to receive offers of new products or services please go into your account and uncheck the box " _Yes, I want to receive information_ ". 

There are two ways in which you may explicitly and intentionally provide us with and consent to our collection of certain personal information: 

Enrollment - If you choose to enroll for one of our products or services, we will request certain information from you. Depending on the type of product or service that you request, you may be asked to provide different personal information. For certain products and services, we may require your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, bank account information, IP address, and/or social security number. Other products and services may require different or supplemental information from you in order to apply. For a detailed listing of the type of personal information requested for our various products, please refer to the enrollment page for the particular product or service. 

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

PaytooMobile.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy for our uses. The following privacy statement discloses our information gathering and dissemention practices for this website: Paytoomobile.com 

The following Privacy Statement explains:

  1. What personally identifiable information Paytoo Mobile .com collects. 
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site. 
  3. What organization collects the information. 
  4. How Paytoo Mobile .com uses the information. 
  5. With whom Paytoo Mobile .com may share user information. 
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Paytoo Mobile .com control. 
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact: [infos@Paytoomobile.com](mailto:infos@Paytoomobile.com)

**Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties.

**Recordings:** While Paymotech Group protects your privacy and data, we want you to be aware that any time you participate in a conference, the Moderator and/or a third-party to the conference may record the session for their own purposes.

**Statistical Information About Your Visit**

When you visit our site, our computers may automatically collect statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally, but rather about a visit to our site. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our site, the user's IP address, which pages people visit, from which domains our visitors come and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit for aggregation purposes only. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our Web site.

**Sending you responses and updates**

We generally respond to any e-mail questions, requests for product or service information, and other inquiries that we receive. We may also retain this correspondence to improve our products, services, and Web site, and for other disclosed purposes. Frequently we retain contact information so that we can send individuals updates or other important information about our services and products. Occasionally these updates or other important information may be sent out by third parties on our behalf. Please be assured that any third party who contacts you in this capacity has executed a confidentiality agreement with us that contains a provision ensuring the privacy and security of any transferred information and limits the third party's use of the shared information to sending updates or providing services on our behalf. In situations where you have supplied your information in connection with a question or request for information about a product or service offered by a Paynet business partner, we may also send the information you have supplied to the Paynet business partners that offer such products or services. Please be assured that these Paynet business partners have agreed to ensure the privacy and security of any transferred information and may only use the shared information to send you information about products or services about which you asked. 

  **Children:  ** Paymotech Group websites are not intended to be accessed by children under the age of 13.  The company does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.  Ordering Paymotech Group products is restricted to adults 18 or older.  However, services acquired for family usage including by minors will produce personal information that will be collected, but attributed to the actual adult subscriber.

 **Your Data**

 **Anonymous Information:** Paymotech Group collects general information that does not personally identify you regarding your use of our sites (“Anonymous Information.”) We may use this Anonymous Information in order to improve our services and products, evaluate our marketing efforts or make our site more useful to you. 

**Email Addresses:** Your email address will be stored just as securely as any other personal information that we have received from you. We will not pass on your email contact information to any unrelated third parties without your expressed permission. We do not wish to send you unwanted email messages or junk mail, however our marketing and accounting departments may need to send you email messages regarding new services and products or regarding accounting or service matters.

**SMS:** We do not wish to send you unwanted SMS/TEXT messages or junk SMS/TEXT, however our marketing and accounting departments may need to send you SMS/TEXT messages regarding new services and products or regarding accounting or service matters.

**Access:** When you register to use any of our services and products, we will send you a confirmation of your registration indicating the personal information that was obtained from your registration. Your registration will be treated as consent to our using your personal and anonymous information in the manner described in this Policy.

**Data Review / Update:** You may review or update the available personally identifiable information that we have received from you online by contacting your local customer service representative. To better safeguard your information, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making appropriate corrections to your information on file.

**Processing payments**

If you use the Paytoo Mobile  Services payment gateway for online transactions, we may provide your personal information to appropriate financial institutions, processors, and third parties under contract with Paynet or our Affiliates for providing a subset of the payment services (for example, credit authorization and fraud screening). For financial institutions and processors, the use of personally identifiable consumer information is governed by federal and state privacy laws. For other third parties under contract with Paytoo Mobile , the use and distribution of your personal information will be used by such entity for its internal use related to fulfilling the transaction services for Paytoo Mobile , will be treated as confidential by this entity, and will be transferred between Paytoo Mobile  and this entity only via encrypted means. We may also permit the merchant through which you placed your order to review the personal information you provide. The merchant's use of your personal information should be governed by your agreement with the merchant. 

If we are required to disclose by law 

If we are required by law to disclose certain information to local, state, federal, national or international government or law enforcement authorities, we will do so.

**Safeguards and Security**

**Our People:  ** We train our people to protect the privacy and security of your sensitive information.  Violations of privacy are subject to sanctions under our corporate policies and by law in various jurisdictions.

 **Our Technology:** The technology we employ helps us protect your sensitive information from loss or misuse, from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction and from improper use. For example, we provide password protection for certain services offered on this site. For our online web reservation service, we use industry standard SSL encryption and proprietary security methods to protect data transmissions and to provide secure sessions. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available and standardized. We store your sensitive information in secure operating environments that are not available to the general public. We have taken all necessary safeguards and security measures to protect your privacy. However, you recognize and accept that under the current technology and practice standards, where Paymotech Group sometimes uses technical security programs in conjunction with its services, Paymotech Group, cannot, and in no way whatsoever provides or implies an absolute warranty of security and protection to you.  If you have agreed to be contacted by email, by providing an email address, than you have thus recognized that all unencrypted Internet email messages can be intercepted and read by third parties.  Hyperlinks: Our website may contain ad banners and hyperlinks that can give you access to websites run by third parties. We have no control over the privacy policies of such third party sites, and we strongly recommend that you review the privacy policy of each third party site that you choose to visit. We are not and cannot be responsible for your privacy on third party sites not under our control.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm>

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. 

**Communications from the Site**  
Special Offers and Updates   
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify username. Established members will occasionally receive information on services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please email [clients@Paytoomobile.com](mailto:clients@paytoomobile.com) to direct you to the respective 'opt' out of such communications. 

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. Users may opt-out of these communications. Please email [clients@paytoomobile.com](mailto:clients@paytoomobile.com) to opt out. 

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

**Sharing**  
 **Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Third Party Intermediaries**  
We use a credit card processing company to process your payments requests. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Paytoomobile.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. 

**Links**  
This Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we Paytoo Mobile  are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every year, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [clients@Paytoomobile.com](mailto:clients@Paytoomobile.com)

 **Children's Guidelines**

Paytoo Mobile .com does:

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. 
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without parental consent. 
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information without prior parental consent. 
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information withoutprior parenta consent. 
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity. 

**  
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the [member information page] or by emailing our Customer Support at [clients@Paytoomobile .com](mailto:clients@paytoomobile.com). 

**  
Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

### Governing Law

Switzerland laws or the appropriate Local laws where the providing company will be registered will govern this Agreement and Your use of the Service.. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this website to the exclusive jurisdiction of the public courts of Switzerland.
